It has begun. Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series.
Let it rain! This is Hana Kojima.
And..,
This way? Or that way? Or..,
Harimakana?
I'm Harimakana.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
So, this is a familiar member of the group,
Today, I would like to look back on the Tokyo Yakanran Vol. 2 held on June 6.
You are the two who were on the show.
It has been a long time. It feels like a long time ago now.
Fans probably have faded memories by now, too. My memory is getting a little hazy.
But really, this is the first time I participated in Vol. 2. Yes, and you started from the very beginning.
We had two consecutive appearances, and the number of participants had increased a little. I see, the first one was quite small.
There were six of us.
The stage was packed, wasn't it? That's right! I was a little worried about whether we could all fit on the stage.
Yes, it was a bit cramped even with six people, but suddenly I wondered if it would be okay.
I was surprised when I tried it. Surprisingly, as long as you get into a comfortable range, you can ride.
No, there came a time when there were only 26 of us. That's right.
That's right. We've been through that before, so it's not so many. Yes, much less.
It's only one digit.
But it's really a lot, and Hanane-san came from Kyushu Jyoshiryoku this time. Yes! From Kyushu Jyoshiryoku. Hanane-chan and others.
Every time. From Osaka. Or from Tohoku.
It's hard to tell. There were a lot of local people,Hard to tell. There were a lot of regional people there,
I could hear the dialects of the local people.
It was so cute.
Even during the rehearsal, dialects were spoken all over the place,
It was really cute.
They knew they shouldn't stop,
I didn't pretend not to hear them,
But I pretended not to,
I thought it was so cute every time.
I thought. That's what I thought.
Even when he was MCing, he was so cute.
She's so cute.
It made me want to be in the film. Yes, I was using a little bit of my mind, wasn't I?
I wanted to change my mind. Like, "I'm going to do something.
Shut up. That's definitely not true.
But I was using Bali or something. Do you know what "bari" is?
Bali means a lot. Really?
Bali means "a lot"? It's like a lot.
Really? What did you think it was?
It's kind of a crunch.
Seriously, what do you really mean?
There's a reason for that. Kanon-chan and I are very good friends and best friends,
We were going to come to Harajuku together.
Was there any scene in the movie?
When we talked about whether or not to use dialect,When we talked about using dialects at that time,
I heard that people like Barry use it a lot, so I tried to imitate him,
I was trying to imitate him, but I didn't know how to use it,
I didn't know how to use it, and then it ended up that I was a statistician,
So what did he mean by that?
I didn't know that, Barry.
Barry, I think you're pretty famous now.
Really?
Isn't that obvious?
What, Barry?
Barry?
Barry is.
Barry's got a lot of Barry.
I didn't know that. I didn't know.
He told me he'd let me know the next time he saw me, and we went straight back to class. I don't get to see him very often.
So I felt like it was a good thing. It was good. I thought you didn't know anything about it.
It's not about that. Not at all. It's not about that. It's not about the dialect.
I've done a lot of songs. It's written here.
First of all, let's look back.
First of all, the River by AKB.
This is the one we all did together.
It was really difficult. This song was really difficult.
The dance moves were terrible. First of all, the beginning was...
It was like, "I can't get in.
I couldn't get into it.I couldn't get in.
It was like that one in rugby.
With the Chinese characters.
I know, I know.
What's it called? That.
Huh!
That's it, that's it. It's a kind of dance.
It was really difficult.
It was difficult to go home, but the nine of us had to get together.
And then, I went to Tokyo.
We all had to dance together at night, so it was all up to Kikkoman.
So, the pressure was definitely not half as great as it should have been.
I felt sorry for him. I felt sorry for him.
But he decided to do it in a really cool way.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's what I'm talking about. If it were me, it would be impossible.
I can't do it. What should I say? You'd definitely do it.
You're going to do it. You'd do it with full confidence.
It's not like I can't do it. Did you find out? I'll say I can't do it.
You do it with full of confidence. I'm sure they'll put up a big front.
Like "Ta-kyah! I think he'll do it in the arena class.
It's too loud. They won't start, will they? Maybe.
The acoustics are a little different. I'm afraid it might be different.
It didn't start well, but thanks to Kikunin, it did.
It started, didn't it? The first song. From now on.It's started. The first song. From now on.
It's a kettle. It started now, didn't it?
And then we'll do the river,
So, there is no magic master disk.
No, there wasn't,
There was one that looked difficult.
Yes, it was.
It's so cute.
It's cute. It was cute.
And then we took over the cuteness,
We took over the cute and made it through the cute,
We did the "kyun kyun kyun kyun" thing, right?
I knew it was good. It's a royal road.
We haven't done that kind of cute stuff so much in our life, right? We haven't done it for 9 years.
We haven't done it for nine years, so I thought it was something that could only be done in this nighttime land.
The 33rd Kyun,
I love you.
For some reason, I suddenly felt like getting up on the platform.
I got on it. I got on the platform.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm so proud of you.
And usually, Mr. Hyugaizaka..,
He has a whispery voice, and you can't tell whether he's saying it or not,
I like you! Don't push me with some kind of pussy.
It's so dull. Oh no.It's so sluggish. Oh no.
Yes, I said something normal.
No, but it seemed like a place of tension.
I did it.
I think it was good.
Did you want to say something? Maybe. A line or something?
I wanted to say it.
You wanted to say it? Yes, I wanted to say it.
I wanted to say it so badly.
I wanted to say it in a cool way.
What? I like you. Like that.
I wanted to do that.
What? Just that one part?
Suddenly, it's from Kana.
I like it.
I want to see that too. On the contrary. On the contrary, I'm curious. What will it be like? Please don't do it.
I'm curious. What do you think? Usually, when I see people doing candy floss, I'm like, "Oh, yeah...".
They make fun of me. They make fun of me so much. It's really cool.
It's a good look.
It's impossible.
I'm trying to be serious.
I always look at him like he's amazing.
His face is no good.
His face makes fun of me.
But..,But..,
But right now, it's a little more fresh and clean, rather than suddenly being cute.
What do you think? Have you changed your mode or something?
I was really, really good in Amehara,
I'm like Kim Taku, right?
That's right.
I really think of myself as Kimura,
But at times like this, I think of myself as Kana Hashimoto.
Just as I once thought.
I change the persona.
I didn't know that. I didn't know that.
It's good to say, "I didn't know that.
Let's try it next time.
If you do it while thinking "I'm Hashimoto Kanna," you'll be invincible. Really.
How's it going? Did you get a lot of fans when you danced with Kyun?
Not so much?
I don't think so.
Even though I thought of you as Kana Hashimoto,
A little bit. I might not have done so much.
Did you?
I didn't.
I don't know.
I was desperate, wasn't I? To dance.
I was pretty desperate. I had to work hard in the lessons, too.That's pretty good. I had to work very hard in my lessons.
And it wasn't hard to catch my breath.
Really. I can't sing anymore.
After the chorus,
It was "Teren teren.
I was singing along.
Can't you turn it around four times? That song.
It's such a cute song,
But it's so hard.
I really thought so.
If you hadn't sung it, you wouldn't have known.
Yeah.
Because everyone sings so freshly, Hinatazaka-san,
I thought we were acting like cute girls at all,
Sing it,
It was like the book couldn't hold its breath.
I thought,
I managed to get through my shift,
And it just went on like that.
Blue lightning.
Smap-san, you know.
That's exactly what Yoo did.
I was dropped off.
So, I was really cool in the lessons. And dancing, too.So I was really cool in my lessons. And dancing, too.
But your costumes were cute.
Yes, they were.
And the choreography was also cute.
This time, it was more pop-oriented.
So I thought it was a little different.
I didn't want to do it in such a cool way.
I added a little bit of cuteness.
I see.
It was a bit of a fine line.
But it was our own version of blue lightning,
Smap's Blue Streak doesn't have a lot of swing,
It's pretty pretentious.
Yes. But this time, we decided to do a cute blue lightning bolt.
You said something like that on the day of rehearsal, didn't you?
Yes. Cute.
On the day of rehearsal, we were told to go with a cute look,
You are a little upset because they told you to make it cuter.
That's right.
I was told on the day of rehearsal, so I was upset, and I didn't know what to do.
We had been performing normally up to that point.
I was thinking, "Is this song going to be cute all of a sudden?
I was like, "What am I going to do?
Everyone was pretty close to Mr. Smap, but the dance was cute, like Mr. Smap is cute.
I don't know what it means, but I thought it was like that,I don't know what it means, but I thought it was like that,
It's like we're all pretending to be cute.
It's not so much a respect for Mr. Smap, but more our own way.
We were all pretending.
But we managed to do it in a cute way.
We also managed to do the blue lightning bolt.
We did it. We made it.
From there, we went into the world of skits.
Harima was just in a play.
A girl who wants to be an actress.
A college high school student.
Kana Narita.
She was indeed a causality.
She's been on many stages, and she's really different.
She was definitely the host of the show.
She was amazing.
Really?
That's right! No, it was almost me.
It was amazing.
No, it was almost me. Seriously.
But it was really loud.
Really? Was it good?
It sounded great. The voices.
There's no microphone.You don't have a microphone.
That's right. So I had no choice but to use my own voice.
I had no choice but to make my voice loud.
Harima had a great advantage there.
That's right. I had to do my best. I had to get it out.
I had to get it out.
It was better than that.
Really? It was good.
It was great.
Thank you. That's all I have to offer.
Don't just say that.
That's my only strength.
That's my strength.
I'm just going to show you my strengths.
After this, I showed you the cutest part of me.
It was cute.
Thank you very much.
Rusty, you know,
You're the most amazing, amazing, amazing person I've ever seen.
You like that part? You know?
I know.
You know?
It fits so well. The voices.
Really?
I've been thinking about the skin on your hands too.I've really been thinking about my hands and skin for a long time.
I did it.
I thought it fit so well.
You should really sing at your birthday party.
Seriously?
You were really good.
I'm so happy.
Yay!
You were so cute.
I've always wanted to sing that part if I was going to sing my cutest part,
I was so happy when she came.
I'm glad.
It was wonderful.
But after I finished my most cute part in a cute way,
I was so happy that they came out and sang that part,
Dancehall?
We sang Dance Hall.
They're good, aren't they? I knew it.
Really?
It's the best fit. It fits.
What do you call it? It's a characteristic of that kind of music.
I don't know. But I often sing male songs,
I was happy. Singing alone.
Thank you for letting me sing.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
You sang alone last time.
Last time, too.
Yes, that's right. I felt like a crown prince.
Stop it.
I thought it was cool.
It's normal.
Thank you.
Some of the other girls sang alone this time,
Kana sang a ballad,
And Chikai sang a cute song,
You are good at showing off.
How should I put it? That's what I'm saying.
You're making fun of me.
You're making fun of me. I mean...
I don't know how to say this kind of song.
You can't make a song like this if you don't have the ability to express yourself. Kana-chan.
Thank you very much.
I thought that was amazing.
I thought you were really good at it.
Thank you.
Dance hall. I can't sing dancehall. I'm sure.
No, but it's really hard.
It's difficult, isn't it? That song.It's hard, isn't it? That song.
It was really difficult.
And this time, the first half and Rei Saho danced behind me,
She was cute.
She was cute, and she danced normally.
She was cute, and she was also dancing normally. The three of us didn't dance.
Sokorosokorosokorosokoros dance hall.
So that's how it is.
That's amazing. Wasn't the dancing pretty intense?
It was intense, and we were in a great hurry to do the rumpelstilts.
That's right.
It's too much. I don't know what to do. I can't remember anything.
I've been saying it for a long time.
I used to watch it when I was a freelancer.
I used to watch it while eating ice cream.
He was watching me. It was amazing.
He was acting like he was having a hard time.
Worst.
Godiva, right?
I was thinking how graceful they were watching me while eating Godiva ice cream.
It was over early.
It was amazing to watch while eating Godiva.
The Godiva ice cream was even better.
I don't want you to watch it.
Then I don't want you to watch it.Then I don't want you to see it.
It's kind of nice.
I was jealous. Have some ice cream.
It was delicious. Ice cream.
I had some, too.
I had a nice ice cream.
It was good.
It was delicious. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.